Rick van der Eijk

Full stack Developer & Unity enthusiast || Javascript, React, CSS, C#, NodeJS & More

General & Motivation

Address: Diaconessenplein 84 Phone number: (+31)628258357
2012 JX Haarlem Email address: rickvdeijk@gmail.com

Date of birth: 03-04-1986

Rick van der Eijk is a self-taught full stack developer who codes highly interactive web apps using Javascript, React, Unity, C#, NodeJS, CSS, and more. He is obsessed with how development and design interact, and wants to create the best user experience possible.

Portfolio: https://portfolio-rick-van-der-eiik.web.app/

Unity game project: https://vdeiik.itch.io/mars-commander

Job Experience

Reflectlab

Freelance Unity & Frontend developer (parttime) August 2022 - Present

 Revamping the Angular frontend of a major B2B webshop system in the horticultural sector.

IBM

March 2021 - August 2022

Fullstack developer

- Coded up a new UI for the Dutch asbestos tracking system at Rijkswaterstaat.
- Developed web applications for other major clients such as Unilever using React, Javascript, Python, CSS, and more.
- Received stellar feedback and project assessments via IBM's official channels.
- Racked up over 300 hours of education via IBM's online learning portal and earned the status of Champion Learner Gold.

Van der Eijk Web Development

January 2020 - present

Fullstack developer

- Available for an additional Unity or web development project from 1 September 2022
- Developing a 3D strategy game in Unity: https://vdeijk.itch.io/mars-commander (2021 2022)
- Built Wordpress websites for multiple clients (2020 2021)
- Coded up a portfolio with a diverse range of projects:
 https://portfolio-rick-van-der-eijk.web.app/ (2020 2021)

 Took highly-rated courses to master Javascript, React, CSS, NodeJS, and more (2020 -2021)

Vendiro, Leiden July 2019 – December 2019

Business Developer

Prospex, Amsterdam Oktober 2016 – June 2019

Inside Sales Rep

Stichting Zeldzame Ziekten Fonds, Den Haag 2015 - 2016 IT/Backoffice Employee & Fundraiser

- Completely redesigned a Customer Relationship Management system so that the organization could systemize its fundraising activities.
- Helped to realize a completely renovated WordPress website (zzf.nl).

Education

Erasmus University Rotterdam 2005 – 2010

Public Administration, Master Governance And Management Of Complex systems.

VWO 1998 - 2004

Specialization Economics & Society

Completed Web Development Courses

- The Modern Angular Bootcamp, <u>udemy.com</u>
- Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More: The Complete Bootcamp 2021, udemy.com
- React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), udemy.com
- React Tutorial and Projects Course, <u>udemv.com</u>
- React Mastering Test Driven Development, udemy.com
- React Styled Components Tutorial and Project Course, udemy.com
- Understanding Typescript 2021 Edition, udemy.com
- The Complete JavaScript Course 2021: From Zero to Expert!, udemy.com
- Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More: The Complete Bootcamp 2021, udemy.com
- Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations and More!, udemy.com

^{*}Rick has work experience via various parttime and fulltime jobs since the age of 13.